<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Statistics on HDB</title>
    <link>https://geturhaineson.netlify.com/tags/statistics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Statistics on HDB</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2017 Yurizal Susanto</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://geturhaineson.netlify.com/tags/statistics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>R Statistics T-test</title>
      <link>https://geturhaineson.netlify.com/blog/r-statistics-t-test/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geturhaineson.netlify.com/blog/r-statistics-t-test/</guid>
      <description>R Series 5Functions qt(), and t.test()Ah t-tests, A t-test is normally an analysis of two populations means through the use of statistical examination; a t-test with two samples is commonly used with small sample sizes, testing the difference between the samples when the variances of two normal distributions are not known. However, there is such a thing as a one sample t-test. The one sample t-test is a statistical procedure used to determine whether a sample of observations could have been generated by a process with a specific mean.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>R Series Proabailities with normal data</title>
      <link>https://geturhaineson.netlify.com/blog/r-series-proabailities-with-normal-data/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geturhaineson.netlify.com/blog/r-series-proabailities-with-normal-data/</guid>
      <description>R Series 4Function pnorm()Let’s talk about normally distributed data. Normally distributed data is the unachievable unicorn, it’s like Kristaps Porzingas, you do everything that you can to get it, but it rarely ever occurs in nature. Normally distributed data is a perfect bell curve and is statistically predictable.Its probability is predictable through a function in R called pnorm. Let’s supposed that a study found that foot lengths for Japanese women are normally distributed with a mean of 24.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>R Basics seq(), rep(), and standard deviation with basic functions</title>
      <link>https://geturhaineson.netlify.com/blog/r-basics-seq-rep-and-standard-deviation-with-basic-functions/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geturhaineson.netlify.com/blog/r-basics-seq-rep-and-standard-deviation-with-basic-functions/</guid>
      <description>R Series 3Functions seq(),rep(), and standard deviationIn the last post we went over significant functions like mean() and diff() this post will examine the seq() or sequence function, the rep() or repeat function, and a way to calculate standard deviation with basic functions.
First, we will examine the sequence function. The sequence function runs by inputing two numbers seperated by a comma in the parenthesis. You then have the option of inputing parameters.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>